

Technical Skills

Languages

JavaScript, ES6 HTML

CSS

CSS frameworks

Bootstrap, Ant design

JavaScript libraries

React

Redux

Key Skills

- Requirement gathering
- Code maintenance
- 3rd party library integration
- Work independently
- Make decisions with minimal supervision

Education

GLA University

B.Tech | CSE (**2016 - 2020**) CGPA - 7.67

Vidya Devi Jindal School

Intermediate - 74.8%

High School - 8.4 CGPA

Raghav Agrawal

8630422423



@raghavagrawal1998

()

@raghavrv98

Personal Profile

M agrawalraghav669@gmail.com

Passionate Frontend web developer with 2+ years of experience in creating and designing web pages in a test-driven environment. Proficient in **React**, **JavaScript**, **HTML** and **CSS**; plus modern JavaScript library such as **Es6**.

Career Summary

Spinny

Front End Developer (Sep 2021 - Present)

Spinny, Gurgaon, Haryana

Front End Developer (June 2020 - Sep 2021)

IOT83, Gurgaon, Haryana

Front End Developer (Intern) (July 2019 - June 2020)

IOT83, Gurgaon, Haryana

Projects:

- Auction Department Spinny
- PMMP (Pipeline Management and Manufacture Program). IOT83
- RS (Raychem Supervisor). **IOT83**

Responsibilities:

- Primarily focused on developing user interface components and implementing them following well-known React workflows (such as Redux).
- Build rich data-driven web pages by consuming RESTful services and APIs.
- Build rich data-driven web pages by consuming GraphhQL APIs.
- Build highly-interactive web pages using modern web technologies such as JavaScript, ES6, HTML5, CSS.
- Actively participated in design and code reviews, to build robust applications.
- Collaborate closely with technical and non-technical counterparts to understand our customers problems.

Key Acheivements:

- Achieved timely delivery of all the goals in an effective & quality-bound manner.
- Developed projects in an agile manner and successfully delivered the sprint.
- Got a **recognition award** for the work and additional bonus for serving the company well.

A small venture ...

Le Thoos

https://lethoos.netlify.app

Le Thoos is a food delivery service. It provides information, menus, and food delivery options from partner restaurants in select areas in Kosi Kalan (Mathura).

Aim: To connect local street food vendors with people.